Location

Johannesburg, Boksburg

Phone 079 690 4666

Email U20435216@tuks.co.za

Nevin Thomas

A passionate IT and Enterprise student with proficiency in programming, business analysis and management, marketing management, and excellent communication skills. My efficiency and effectiveness in these areas have been honed through years of experience and continuous learning. I am confident in my ability to deliver high-quality work and meet project objectives within the given time frame. My strong communication skills enable me to effectively collaborate with team members and customers, ensuring that all parties are aligned towards achieving the desired outcomes.

Experience

MathU Teaching Program | Feb 2022 - Dec 2023

- Designed and created program materials and resources to communicate program activities and outcomes to students
- Implemented a variety of teaching strategies, such as group work, project-based learning, and hands-on experiments, to ensure student understanding
- Optimized video projects for various platforms, resulting in improved video playback and engagement

Kashcarry Spare Parts Shop| June 2022 - July 2023

- I was employed as a sales representative at a commercial enterprise and acquired valuable interpersonal skills.
- Engaging in the operation and utilization of computer technology and sales systems.

Education

University of Pretoria | BSc Information and Knowledge Systems | Jan 2021 - Dec 2024

I have learnt proficient programming skills, expanded my knowledge working with hardware tools and interacting with people to derive solutions and solve issues effectively.

Key skills and characteristics

- Microsoft Office Suite
- Strong Collaboration and Leadership Skills
- Analytical Thinking Skills
- Data Analysis
- Hardware Tool Skills